# LÊ VĂN HÙNG

Java Backend Staff



#### **Contact information**

- 10/03/1995
- Nam
- 0326817904
- ✓ levanhung10395@gmail.com
- 🖀 🖰 Đà Nẵng
- https://github.com/ITBusy

# **Skills**

#### **Good At Backend**

- Java, OOP, JDBC, JSP & servlet, Hibernate,
JPA, Spring boot

#### **Database**

- SQL, Firebase

#### Mobile

- React native

#### Front-end

- HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- jQuery, Bootstrap 5, Ajax jQuery
- Angular Cli
- ReactJS

#### Git

Have experience on git with individual project

#### **English**

Can read English documents

# **Career goals**

With specialized knowledge of Spring Framework and Hibernate, SQL and database, Java Core & OOP, HTML, CSS and JavaScript. I would like to find a job as a Java programmer in a professional and dynamic working environment so that I can promote my ability in developing quality software products using Java language. The challenging working environment is the motivation and opportunity for me to perfect my professional knowledge, become an excellent programmer and join the core staff of the company in the coming time.

### **Education**

# **FPT Polytechnic College**

10/2020-Now

Software Technology

# Work experience

#### Sales website

02/2022-05/2022

FPT Polytechnic College

- Link: https://github.com/ITBusy/Laptopshop.git
- Number of members: Individual
- Technology performed: spring boot, ajax, html, css
- Functional description: CRUD

#### Sales website 2

05/2022-07/2022

FPT Polytechnic College

- Link backend spring boot: https://github.com/ITBusy/backend.git
- Link Frontend Angular Cli: https://github.com/ITBusy/website-sales.git
- Number of members: Individual
- Technology performed: spring boot, angular cli, firebase, jwt security, html, css
- Functional description: CRUD, put image on firebase, security by jwt...

# LE HOANG BINH MINH

Fresher Back-End Developer (Java)



# **Contact information**

- Feb24, 2002
- Male
- 0336039532
- HoaKhanh, LienChieu, DaNang
- https://github.com/MinhDev0010

#### **Skills**

# Language

English

#### **Database**

SQL Server, My SQL

# Front-end

- HTML/CSS, Javascript
- -JQuery,BootStrap 4

# Back-end

- Java, OOP, JDBC, Jsp & Serverlet, Hibernate,Jpa, Spring boot

### Git

Have experience on git with individual project

# **Objective**

I am a final year student majoring in Information Technology in Java Backend. With the professional knowledge that has been learned, I want to find the right internship job that is the position of java backend staff and promote my ability well. The practical work experience you have accumulated will be the basis for you to achieve your goal of becoming a good network management expert in the next 5 years

### **Education**

### **FPT Polytechnic College**

October 2020-Now

Final year students

# Work experience

### **Project 1**

12/2021-Present

FPT Polytechnic College

Git link: https://github.com/MinhDev0010/QuanLyCaFe.git

Number of members: individual

- Number of members: Individual

- Technology performed: java swing

- Functional description: CRUD

#### **Project 2**

12/2021-Now

FPT Polytechnic College

Git link: https://github.com/MinhDev0010/Java5.git

Number of members: Individual

- Technology performed: spring boot, ajax, html, css

- Functional description: CRUD

#### Other projects:

12/2021-Now

FPT Polytechnic College

Link:https://github.com/MinhDev0010

#### **Interests**

I like soccer, music.. © topcv.vn